Guide to the Roland Park Company Records, ca. 1891-1962
Roland Park Company Records, ca. 1891-1962
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Roland Park Company records, ca.1891-1962
2828
Roland Park Company.
407 cubic ft.
Correspondence, ledgers, sales department files, annual reports, architectural approval records, articles of incorporation, architectural specifications, minutes, scrapbooks, photographs, contracts and deeds, blueprints, renderings, and maps.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, ledgers, sales department files, annual reports, architectural approval records, articles of incorporation, architectural specifications, minutes, scrapbooks, photographs, contracts and deeds, blueprints, renderings, and maps for the projects of the Roland Park Company around Baltimore, including Guilford, Homeland, Loch Raven, Northwood Apartments, Kernwood, Woodburne, and Pentridge. Major correspondents are Edward H. Bouton and John Mowbray; Frederick Law Olmsted, Jr., Edward L. Palmer, Jr., and George Kessler are also represented.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Roland Park Company was established in 1891 to plan and develop a residential area north of the city limits of Baltimore, Maryland. The company was owned by the Lands Trust Company of London, England, and the Jarvis-Conklin Mortgage Company, headquartered in Kansas City, served as the developer. Edward H. Bouton, a Kansas City real estate developer, served as the company's general manager. Landscape architects George Kessler, John C. Olmsted and Frederick Law Olmsted, Jr. were involved with the planning of Roland Park. By 1910, Roland Park neared completion, and the company reorganized and continued to plan other residential areas, among them Guilford, Homeland and Northwood.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, ledgers, sales department files, annual reports, architectural approval records, articles of incorporation, architectural specifications, minutes, scrapbooks, photographs, contracts and deeds, blueprints, renderings, and maps for the projects of the Roland Park Company around Baltimore, including Guilford, Homeland, Loch Raven, Northwood Apartments, Kernwood, Woodburne, and Pentridge. Major correspondents are Edward H. Bouton and John Mowbray; Frederick Law Olmsted, Jr., Edward L. Palmer, Jr., and George Kessler are also represented.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Roland Park Company.; Bouton, Edward H.; Kessler, George.; Mowbray, John.; Olmsted, Frederick Law, Jr.
Subjects:
Apartment houses.; Architecture--Maryland--Baltimore.; City planning--Maryland--Baltimore.; Community development, Urban.
Places:
Baltimore (Md.)--City planning.; Guilford (Md.)--City planning.; Homeland (Md.)--City planning.; Northwood (Md.)--City planning.; Roland Park (Md.)--City planning.
Form and Genre Terms:
Architectural drawings.; Blueprints.; Deeds.; Ledgers.; Maps.; Photographs.; Scrapbooks.; Specifications.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Correspondence
Boxes 1-42, 57-245
Series II. Miscellaneous materials
Boxes 246-342
Series III. Edward L. Palmer, Jr.'s 1917 correspondence
Boxes 106-112, 117
Series IV. Bound volumes
Box 341, bound volumes on shelf
Series V. Ledgers and portfolios
Boxes 344-351, bound volumes on shelf
Series VI. Record plats for Guilford
Mapcase
Series VII. Record plats not held by Cornell
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Correspondence
  - A, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ba-Be, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ba, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bi, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bo, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bo-By, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ca, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ce-Cl, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Co, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Cr-Cy, 1891-1895 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Da-Di, 1893-1894 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Do-Dy, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - E, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fa-Fl, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Fo, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Fr-Fy, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ga-Gn, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Go-Gr, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ha-Hel, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Hem-Ho, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Hu-Hy, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - I-J, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - K, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Kessler, George, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - La-Lez, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Lh-Ly,Mc, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Ma, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Me-My, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - N, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - N, 1893-1894 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - N, P, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - P, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 32-34)
  - Telegrams, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Ra-Re, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Ri, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Ro-Ru, 1892-1894 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sa-Sb, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Sc, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Se-Sh, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Si-Sr, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Sta-Ste, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ste, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Sti-Sw, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Ta-Th, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ti-Ty, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - U-Wa, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Wal-War, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - War-Waz, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - We-Wiz, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Wo-Wy, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Y-Z, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Telegrams, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Dec.-Sept., 1892 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Aug.-July, 1892, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - June, 1892, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - May-Apr., 1892, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Mar.-Jan., 1892, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Dec.-June, 1891 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Dec.-Nov., 1893-1894 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Oct.-Sept., 1893-1894 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Aug.-June, 1893-1894 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - May-Jan., 1893-1894 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Telegrams, 1891-1894 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Dec.-July, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - June-Apr., 1895 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Mar.-Jan., 1895 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Telegrams, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - A-L, 1904-1905 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - M-S, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - T-Z, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Telegrams, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - A-F, 1893-1894 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - G-J, 1893-1894 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - K-O, 1893-1894 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - P-Z, 1893-1894 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - A-C, 1894-1895 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - D-F, 1895-1896 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - G-H, 1895-1896 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - I-N, 1895-1896 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - K, 1895-1896 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - T-Z, 1895-1896 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - H, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - J,L, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - M, 1894-1895 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - N, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - O-R, 1895-1896 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - S, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - T-V, 1894-1895 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - W, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - W-Z, 1894-1895 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Telegrams, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - A-D, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - E-M, 1893-1894 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - N-S, 1894-1895 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - T-Z, 1893-1894 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Lot Receipts, 1892 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Lot Receipts, 1893 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Lot Receipts, 1893-1894 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Lot Receipts, 1892, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Lot Receipts, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Lot Receipts, 1897 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Lot Receipts, 1898 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Lot Receipts, 1899 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Lot Receipts, 1900 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Lot Receipts, 1901 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Lot Receipts, 1902 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Lot Receipts, 1903 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Lot Receipts, 1903-1904 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Lot Receipts, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Lot Receipts, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - A-B, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - C, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - D,E, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - F, G, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - A, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - B, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - C, 1892 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - D, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - E-G, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - H, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 27-28)
  - I-K, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - L-M, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - M, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - M, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - N, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - N-O, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - P, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Q-S, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - S, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - T-W, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - W, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - X-Z, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Telegrams, 1895-1896 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - A-K Lake Roland Elevated Railroad Co., 1892-1893 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - S-W Lake Roland Elevated Railroad Co., 1892-1893 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Telegrams Lake Roland Elevated Railroad Co., 1893 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - A, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - B, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
  - C, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - D, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - E, F, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - G, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 20-21)
  - H, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 22-23)
  - I, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - J, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - K, L, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - M, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 27-28)
  - N-O, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - P-Q, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - R-S, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - S, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 4-6)
  - T, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - U-W, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - W, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - X-Z, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Telegrams, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - A-D [Bouton?], 1897-1898 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - E-H [Bouton?], 1897-1898 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - I-M [Bouton?], 1897-1898 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - N-S [Bouton?], 1897-1898 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - T-Z [Bouton?], 1897-1898 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Telegrams [Bouton?], 1897-1898 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - A, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - B, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - C, D, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - E-G, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - G-H, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - H-J, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - K-L, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - M, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - M-P, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - T-V, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - W, 1898 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - W-Z, 1898 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Telegrams, 1898 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - A-C Roland Park Country Club, 1898-1899 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - D-J Roland Park Country Club, 1898-1899 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - K-L Roland Park Country Club, 1898-1899 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - M-N Roland Park Country Club, 1898-1899 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - O Roland Park Country Club, 1898 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - P-Z Roland Park Country Club, 1898-1899 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Telegrams Roland Park Country Club, 1898-1899 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - A-B, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - B, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - C, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - D-F, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - G, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - H, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - I-K, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - L-M, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - M, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - N-Q, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - R, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - S, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - S-V, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - W, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Y-Z, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Telegrams, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - A, 1900 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - B, 1900 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - C, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - C, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - D, 1898 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - E, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - F-G, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - H, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - H-J, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - K-L, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - M, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - M-N, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - O, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - P, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - R, S, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - S, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - S, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - T-V, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - W, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - W-Z, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Telegrams, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - B,C, 1899-1901 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - E-F, 1899-1901 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - G, H, 1899-1901 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - H, 1899-1901 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - K-M, 1899-1901 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - P-R, 1899-1901 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - S-Z, 1899-1901 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Telegrams, 1899-1901 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - A-C [Bouton?], 1900 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - D-G, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - H-K, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - M-S, 1900 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - T-Z, 1900 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - A-D [Bouton?], 1901 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - E-L, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - M-S, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - T-Z, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - A, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - B, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - B, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - B, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - C, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - C, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - C, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - C, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - D, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - E, F, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - F, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Freight Receipts, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - G, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - G, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - H, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - H, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - I, J, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - K, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - L, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - L, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - M, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - M, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - N, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - O, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - P, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - R, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - S, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - S, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - S, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - S, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - T, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - U-V, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - W, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - W, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Wyatt and Notting, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Wyatt and Notting, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Y-Z, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Telegrams, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - A-L, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - L, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - M, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - P, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - R-S, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - T-W, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - A-C, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - D-K, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - M-R, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - S, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - S-T, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - W-Z, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - A-B, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - C-E, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - E-G, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - H-M, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - M-P, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - U-W, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - A-H, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - K-N, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - O, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - R-S, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - V-Y, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - A-D, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - E-F, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - G-H, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - H-M, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - P-W, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - A-C, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - F-J, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - M-S, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - T-W, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - A-D, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - E-G, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - H-R, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - S-Y, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - A-G, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - G, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - H-M, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - P-Z, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - A-F, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - G-M, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - N, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - R-Z, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - A-H, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - I-L, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - A-B, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - C-E, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - F-M, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - M-O, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - P-S, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - T-Z, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Telegram, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - A-G Balto Country Club, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - H-M Balto Country Club, 1900-1901 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - N-Z Balto Country Club, 1900-1901 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Telegrams Balto Country Club, 1900-1901 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - A-D, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - E-P, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - R-T, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - U-Z, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - A-C, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - D-O, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - P-Z, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - B-F, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - G-M, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - N-V, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Telegrams, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - A-M, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - N-W, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - A-G, 1902 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - H-M, 1902 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - N-V, 1902 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - W, 1902 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Telegrams, 1902 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - I-L, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - L-M, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - M-N, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - A-B Balto Country Club, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - C-D, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - F-J, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - K-R, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - S-Y, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - B, 1904 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - B, 1904 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - P-Q, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - R-S, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - S-T, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - W-Z, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - A-H, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - L-O, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - P-S, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - T-Z, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - A-G, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - H-M, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - O-P, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - S, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - T-Z, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Telegrams, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - A-L, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - M-P (Platt), 1903 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - R-W, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - G-M, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - P-S, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - W, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - A-B, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - C-D, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - E-U, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - B, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - C-G, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - H-M, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - P-W, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - A-G, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - H-L, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - M-O, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - P-Y, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - A-L, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - M-R, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - S-W, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - A-C, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - D-H, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - K-M, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - N-W, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - A-D, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - G-J, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - K-M, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - N-W, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - B-P, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - R-S, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - T, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - B-L, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - N-S, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - B-M, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - O-W, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - A-C, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - D-J, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - K-R, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - S-Y, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - A, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - B, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - C-D, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - E-G, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - H, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - A-H Bouton Personal [Conklin re expanded Roland Park], 1903 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - M-T Bouton Personal, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Telegrams, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - A-C, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - H-L, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - M-W, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - A-B, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - C-P, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - S, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - S, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - W, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - A-B, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - C-P, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - S-U, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - A-H, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - K-O [Olmsted], 1904 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - R-Z, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - B, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - B-G, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - J-T, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - A-M, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - N-S, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - T-Y, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - A-F, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - G-K, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - M-O, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - P-W, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - A-L, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - M-T, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - W-Y, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - A-G, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - H-M, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - P-W, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - A-M, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - N, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - R-V, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - B-D, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - G-L, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - M-P, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - R-W, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - A-H, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - M-O, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - C, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - D, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - E-F, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - G-H, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - H-J, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - K-L, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - M, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - M-N, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - O, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - P-Q, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - R, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - S, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - S-T, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - T, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - W, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - W, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - A-C Bouton personal and country club, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - D-G Bouton personal and country club, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - H-M Bouton personal and country club, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - N-S Bouton personal and country club (some Olmsted), 1904 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - S-Y Bouton personal and country club, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - A-C, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - D-J, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - K-S, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - T-Y, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Telegrams, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - A-B, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - B, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - B, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - C, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - H-W (Charles Platt correspondence), 1905 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - A-C, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - C, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - G-M, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - T-W (Wyatt and Nolting), 1905 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - A-B, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - C-D, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - E-M, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - P-W, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - A-N, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - O (Olmsted), 1905 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - P-Y, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - B, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - B, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - C-G, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - H, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - I-W, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - B-D, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - J-R, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - S-T, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - W-Y, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - A-D, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - E-L, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - M-O, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - P-S, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - T-Y, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - A-C, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - G-H, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - K-M, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - M-P, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - S-W, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - A-N, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - N, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - N, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - N, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - R-W, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - B-C, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - D-L, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - M-P, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - R-S, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - T-W, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Response to employment advertisement, Feb. 1905 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Response to employment advertisement, Feb. 1905 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - C-O, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - P-S, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - A-C, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - E-O, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - P-S, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - T, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - T-W, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - B-C, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - E-G, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - H-L, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - M-S, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - T-W, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - A-B, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - C-F, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - G-M, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - M-R, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - S-W, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - B-H, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - I-P, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - S-V, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - W, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - W, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - A-H, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - L-P, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - S-W, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - W, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - A-B, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - C-F, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - G-K, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - L-P, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - R-S, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - C-F, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - G-L, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - M-P, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - R-Z, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - A, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - B, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - C, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - D, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 1)